我之前看了一部电影预告
Hey, so I saw a movie trailer the other day.
蝙蝠侠怎么可能打得过超人呢
How could Batman possibly fight Superman?
真是瞎透了
I mean, isn't that dumb?
或许他用了氪气石
Maybe he uses Kryptonite.
来自超人故乡氪星的一种矿物
有令氪星人失去超能力等多种功效
蝙蝠侠超有钱
Well, Batman's got a lot of money.
或许他用钱打造出具有类似超人能力的装甲
Maybe he builds a suit that can do everything Superman can do.
不不不不不
No, no, no, no, no.
这样的电影我看过  叫《钢铁侠》
I've seen that movie. It's called Iron Man.
怎么回事
What is happening?
我不知道
I don't know.
但这画面太美了
But it's beautiful.
而且蝙蝠侠换本·阿弗莱克演了
And now Ben Affleck is Batman?
他在《恋爱中的莎士比亚》那部里演得很棒
Oh, he was great in Shakespeare in Love.
我们下次闺蜜之夜应该来看这部
Ooh, we should watch that next girls' night.
我们可以再配上
We could do a double feature
莱昂纳多的《罗密欧与朱丽叶》啊
with the Leonardo DiCaprio Romeo + Juliet.
我可乐意看小李子了
Oh, I love me some Leo.
美景消失了
And it's gone.
大家安安
Oh, hello, everyone.
很开心跟大家宣布本皇龙体已有好转
I am happy to report I'm feeling much better.
"恭喜"
Good for you.
发烧已退  鼻子也通
My fever is gone, my sinuses are pressure-free,
痰也清澈得像国家公园里的瀑布水一样
and my mucus is as clear as a Yosemite waterfall.
"棒呆了"
Glad to hear it.
明日我就能回归工作岗位了
I'll be able to return to work tomorrow.
"赞"
Yay.
大家怎么都不开心呢
Well, why isn't everyone happy?
你们的小太阳准备重新发光发热啦
Your little ray of sunshine is ready to beam again.
-你真的不知道为什么吗  -不知道
- You really don't know why? - No.
但我听出他那声"赞"是在讽刺
But I knew that his "yay" was sarcastic.
上次出恭时  声响犹如雨打芭蕉的这位
Not bad for a guy whose last bowel movement
居然还有体力讽刺  不赖嘛
sounded like rain on a roof.
让我帮忙你回忆一下
Let me refresh your memory.
佩妮
Penny,
帮我在胸口抹清凉油
rub Vicks on my chest.
谢尔顿  我给你做了早饭
Sheldon, I cooked you breakfast.
铺了床
I made your bed.
检查你嘴里有没有鹅口疮
I checked your mouth for thrush.
清凉油你可以自己抹
You can rub your own chest.
行行行  世上的男人 你都没少摸过
Oh, sure, grope every other male on the planet,
到我这儿就装清纯
but draw the line with me.
我从公司给你准备了这个康复小袋袋
I brought you a little care package from work.
里面有我们最新的抗病毒药
It's our latest antiviral
还有我们最好的抗鼻塞药
and the best decongestant we make.
那我希望笑是最好的药物
I hope laughter is the best medicine,
因为这包东西根本就是在搞笑
'cause this care package is a joke.
她大老远特意跑来...
Hey, she came all the way here...
你记得饭后再吃啊
You're gonna want to take these with food.
谢尔顿  别孩子气了
Sheldon, stop being a baby
让艾米丽给你看看嘛
and let Emily take a look at you.
她是皮肤科医生
She's a dermatologist.
我上过医学院啊
I went to medical school.
这样的话  那请你把位于你旁边的
Well, in that case, try removing the irritating patch
那坨烦人棕色皮肤给去除掉
of brown skin standing next to you.
来  吃吧
All right, here you go.
莱纳德  我要死了
Leonard, I'm dying.
你才不会死  只是流感而已
You're not dying. It's just the flu.
我要的是鸡汤面
I asked for chicken noodle.
这个是鸡与星星状的面  我要气死了
This is chicken and stars. It's killing me.
我最终还是没吃到鸡汤面不是吗
I never did get that chicken noodle, did I?
翻译：毒舌呛声赛太公  嫌东嫌西YY猫
猫中之王
谢尔顿
Hi, Sheldon.
你好啊
Hello.
你身体好点了吗
Are you feeling any better?
生理上好点了  但心里不太好
Physically, yes, but I'm upset
因为大家莫名其妙就不爽我
because everyone's mad at me for no good reason.
你跟我说说发生了什么吧
Why don't you tell me what happened,
然后我会用温和  慈爱的方式
and in a gentle, loving way,
来跟你解释你为什么错了
I'll explain to you why you're wrong.
你知道当人生病的时候
You know how, when you're sick,
是有权对身旁或任何人耍脾气
you're allowed to be cranky and say whatever you want
而且完全不用鸟他们感受的吧
and other people's feelings don't matter?
温和慈爱  这有点费劲啊
Gentle and loving-- this is gonna be tricky.
我都烧到38.3度了
I had a 101 fever.
此时不尖酸刻薄对亲朋好友  更待何时
If that's not a time to verbally abuse my loved ones, when is?
谢尔顿  当你生病的时候  你会有点...
Sheldon, when you're sick, you can be...
让人受不了
unbearable.
所以你的小伙伴们
That's why your friends have been known
要么加班  要么溜去看电影
to work late or sneak out to the movies
或者多留在神经生物学大会
or stay at a neurobiology conference
哪怕大会三天前就结束了
three days after it's ended.
你多留在密歇根就是为了要躲我吗
You stayed in Michigan all week to avoid being around me?
不是不是  不止如此
No, no, not just that.
还有...
I mean...
底特律下雨夹雪的时候特美呢
Detroit is beautiful when it's sleeting.
又不是只有我一个人生病时
You know, I'm not the only one
才这么讨人厌
who's unpleasant when they're sick.
像佩妮食物中毒的那次  她呕吐声大到
When Penny got food poisoning, she threw up so loudly
我都听不到电视的声音了
I could barely hear the television.
我好像听到了什么声音
Ooh, I just heard something.
不知道是冰雹声还是枪声
Might be hail, might be gunfire.
反正我都要去拍照围观啦  再见
Either way, I'm gonna go take pictures. Bye.
斯图尔特
Hey, Stuart.
谢尔顿呢
Hey. Where's Sheldon?
-还病着呢  -没  已经好了
- Still sick? - No, he's fine.
我们只是需要喘口气
We just needed a little break.
我理解
Yeah, I get that.
我那天送漫画去给他的时候
When I brought him his comics the other day,
他说"靠  索命鬼真的来了"
he said, "Oh, great, Death is literally at my door."
他对每个人都是这么贱
He was being a jerk to everyone.
你别往心里去
Don't take it personally.
我吃着无数种抗抑郁药
Oh, I'm on so many antidepressants,
我就是想难过都没办法
I couldn't if I wanted to.
真希望我们能甩开谢尔顿做更多事
I wish we could do more stuff without Sheldon.
我一直这么真心希望
I wish that all the time.
通常都是在我吹熄生日蛋糕之前
Usually before I blow out birthday candles.
艾米就甩开他休息了一阵子啊
You know, Amy took some time off from him.
感情还因此提升了不少
Really improved their relationship.
行
Okay.
只要最后我们不需要跟他滚床单
As long as it doesn't end with us having coitus with him,
我就加入
I'm in.
我们应该一起去旅游之类的
We should all take a trip or something.
我跟佩妮谈过
You know, Penny and I have been talking
找个周末去赌城玩
about taking a weekend in Vegas.
或许我们大伙应该一起去
Maybe we should all go.
妮妮肯定想去
Bernie would love that.
或许我们可以叫台派对巴士载我们去
Maybe we could get one of those party buses to take us there.
听起来就很有意思
That sounds really fun.
绝对有意思
Yeah, that sounds fun.
派对巴  派对趴
A party-bus party don't stop.
我说"派对"  你说"巴"
When I say "party," you say "bus."
-不  -不
- No. - No.
- No. - No!
今天我们几个男的在讨论
So, the guys and I were talking about
租一台派对巴士  大家一起去赌城玩
renting a party bus and everyone going to Vegas.
感觉应该挺有意思
Oh, that could be fun.
但我先问清楚  你说派对巴士
But just to be clear, you mean a party bus
是指有酒跟音乐的那种吧
with booze and music, right,
不是盒装果汁搭配游戏机
not, like, juice boxes and video games?
是啦
Yes.
上次霍华德的生日趴是送孩子去玩的那种
And Howard's birthday was a drop-off party.
你这"家长"明明不用留下的
You didn't have to stay.
那我加入
Well, I'm in.
-我们什么时候出发  -这周末
- When are we going? - This weekend.
我们要去哪里玩啊
Oh, where are we going?
赌城  但是...
Well, Vegas, but...
没有特产太妃糖的大西洋城[也是赌城]吗
Ugh, Atlantic City without the taffy?
我可不想去
No, thank you.
没关系  其实也没有要邀请你
That's fine, 'cause actually you're not invited.
真的假的  太伤人了
Well, now... well, that's hurtful.
谢尔顿  你根本不喜欢那地方
Oh, Sheldon, you don't even like it there.
我能把一个地方看做小便池里的芳香剂
I can consider a place America's urinal cake
但我去的时候也还是尿得享受啊
and still enjoy the occasional visit.
这次不行
Not this time.
算了  那我跟沃罗威茨玩吧
Oh, fine. Then I'll just hang out with Wolowitz.
他也去
He's coming, too.
-那我和拉杰...  -他也去
- Well, then Raj and I will... - Nope.
很好  那我找斯图尔特
Very well. Stuart.
好呀  去吧
Oh, great. Do that.
恶  斯图尔特
Ugh. Stuart.
谢尔顿  有啥新鲜事吗
Hi, Sheldon. What's new?
我们的朋友是混蛋  我气他们所有人
Our friends are jerks, and I'm mad at all of them.
我是问"有啥新鲜事"  不过算了
I said, "What's new?" but sure.
你能相信他们打算组团去
Can you believe they planned a trip
赌城玩却不邀请我吗
to Las Vegas and didn't invite me?
你是不是拒绝道歉
Did you refuse to apologize
还表现得他们生气是愚蠢的表现呀
and act like they were stupid for being mad?
我更喜欢我们之前的感情
You know, I liked it better when there was still
留有一丝丝神秘感
a little mystery left in our relationship.
大家都努力去照顾你
Everyone tried to take care of you,
而你只会对他们毒舌嫌弃
and you were nothing but mean to them.
真不敢相信你居然不站我这边
I can't believe you're not on my side.
有人偷了你的汽车音响时  我可是站你这边
I was on your side when someone stole your car radio.
你不站我这边  你还能站谁那边啊
Who else's side could you have been on?
难说啊
I don't know.
说不定窃贼是个热爱音乐的高尚流浪汉
A music-loving hobo with a heart of gold?
谢尔顿  我理解你不高兴
Sheldon, I understand that you're upset
因为觉得自己被孤立
because you feel left out,
但我不明白这事有啥好浪费时间讨论
but I don't know why we're even talking about this.
去跟他们道歉就对了
Just apologize to them.
如果要这样才能加入他们的白痴之旅  那行吧
Fine, if that's what it takes to go on their dumb trip.
或许你可以试着
Maybe you could try apologizing
真的因为觉得内疚而道歉
because you actually feel bad.
这叫同理心
It's called empathy.
这方面你可以提升一下
It's something you could work on.
我有同理心啊
I have empathy.
请看
Watch.
莱纳德为我煮汤  我却嫌东嫌西
Leonard made me soup, and I was mean to him.
非常好
Great.
现在试试像个正常人一样讲话
Now try it as if this isn't your first day as a person.
行
Fine.
莱纳德为我煮汤  我却嫌东嫌西
Leonard made me soup, and I was mean to him.
哎哟  我有点感觉了
Hey, I felt a little something.
我再试试
Let me try again.
莱纳德为我煮汤  我却嫌东嫌西
Leonard made me soup, and I was mean to him.
我的确嫌东嫌西了
I was mean to him.
他肯定不好受
He must have felt terrible.
现在我也觉得不好受了
Oh, now I feel terrible.
真是妙啊
Neat!
很高兴能帮上忙
Glad I could help.
现在让我看看你因为撒谎
Now let me see you feel bad for lying
故意在底特律待着不走而内疚的样子
and staying in Detroit longer than you needed to.
我觉得非常非常内疚
I feel so, so bad.
看来咱俩很擅长这个嘛
Hey, we're both great at this.
莱纳德  准备接受道歉
Leonard, get ready for an apology.
而跟奈特·沙马兰拍的电影不一样的地方是
And with the added twist of an M. Night Shyamalan movie,
我打算真心来做
I'm going to mean it.
所以就像任何一部
Ah, so like every other
我看过的奈特·沙马兰电影那样
M. Night Shyamalan movie I've seen,
你提前剧透了
you spoil it in advance.
如果你没发现《第六感》的主角其实是死人
Hey, if you didn't know Bruce Willis was dead the whole time,
那可不能怪我
that's not on me.
好吧
Okay.
我要说了
Here it comes.
我生病的时候  你努力照顾我
You tried to take care of me when I was sick,
而我却对你嫌东嫌西
and I was mean to you.
没有任何理由可以这样做
There's no excuse for that.
我真的很抱歉
And I'm truly sorry.
谢谢
Thank you.
谢谢你的道歉
I appreciate that.
我想让你知道这是发自内心的
I want you to know that that is sincere.
我的确觉得内疚
I-I do feel bad.
我这么说不是为了要加入你们的旅行
I'm not just saying it to be included on your trip.
那真是多谢了
Appreciate that, too.
太好了
Terrific.
现在就剩你邀请我加入了
Now all that's left is for you to invite me to come.
我会问  "你确定吗"
Me to ask, "Are you sure?"
你就说  "当然啦"
You to say, "Absolutely."
然后我以这句话收尾
And then me to bring it home with,
"看着你的小脸  我怎么忍心拒绝呢"
"How could I say no to that face?"
你还是不能来
You're still not coming.
什么  但我道歉了  也是真心的啊
What? But I apologized and I meant it.
我知道我们不经常玩这游戏
I know that we don't play this game very often,
但你玩的方式不对
but you're doing it wrong.
谢尔顿  我接受你的道歉
Sheldon, I accept your apology,
但你生病的时候让很多人不爽
but you upset a lot of people while you were sick.
所以你能不能来  不是我说了算
I'm not in a position to just say you can come.
那好吧
Well, all right.
那如果我向他们所有人道歉呢
What if I apologize to all of them?
好吧  如果你向每一个人道歉
Fine, if you apologize to everyone,
他们都觉得可以  那当然  你可以来
they all say it's okay, then yes, you can come.
接受挑战
Challenge accepted!
谢尔顿·库珀道歉之旅开始啦
Sounds like it's time for the Sheldon Cooper Apology Tour.
我"希望"这跟
Well, I hope it's as much fun
谢尔顿·库珀当地菜单拼写检查之旅一样有趣
as the Sheldon Cooper Spell-Checks Local Menus Tour.
我的老天
My goodness!
你还记得"菜内含炉笋"吗
Do you remember "Comes with apsparagus"?
霍华德和伯纳黛特
Howard and Bernadette,
我生病的时候  你们想帮我减轻痛苦
you tried to comfort me when I was ill,
我却对你们非常不客气
and I treated you terribly.
对不起
I'm sorry.
真是想不到
I'm impressed.
别插嘴  我还没完
No, no, no, wait. I'm not done.
容我用我的排箫
Allow me to underscore my sentiment
吹一曲布兰达·李的《对不起》
with a haunting rendition
通过令人难忘的演奏
of Brenda Lee's "I'm Sorry"
来强调我的真心
played on the pan flute.
-道歉接受  -原谅你  原谅你
- Apology accepted! - Forgiven, forgiven!
好吧  八个小时的练习付诸东流
All right, that's eight hours of practice down the drain.
为了纪念这一时刻
And to memorialize this occasion,
这是你们的纪念T恤
here are your commemorative T-shirts.
"谢尔顿·库珀向我道歉了"
"Sheldon Cooper apologized to me""
"他让大家都开心了"
"And he made it all better."
你的确给予我
All you did was offer
母亲般的照料和关爱
maternal care and affection,
而得到的回报确是
and all you received in return
我无礼和冷漠的行为
was rude and insensitive behavior.
不能等会再说吗
Can this wait?
恐怕不行
I'm afraid it can't.
明天就启程了
The trip is tomorrow.
我还要向其他人道歉呢
And I have more apologies to make.
好吧  我接受你的道歉  快走吧
Okay, fine, I accept your apology, now get out!
太好了  你不介意拿着这件T恤
Wonderful. Would you mind holding up this shirt
-让我拍一张快...  -莱纳德
- while I take a quick...? - Leonard!
我不舒服的时候  你给我送来漫画书
You brought me my comic books when I wasn't feeling well.
那十分贴心
That-that was thoughtful.
而我十分不体谅你心意
And I was insensitive.
对不起
I'm sorry.
谢谢你  谢尔顿
Thank you, Sheldon.
谢谢你的道歉
I appreciate that.
我想让你知道我是发自内心的
And I want you to know that I mean it, you know?
不是因为我想加入赌城之旅
This isn't me just wanting to go on the trip to Las Vegas.
什么赌城之旅
What trip to Las Vegas?
就是这个周末大家一起坐派对巴士去啊
The one everyone's taking this weekend on the party bus.
当然  没人邀请我
Of course, I wasn't invited.
我是这么理解的
That would be my understanding.
让我们换一个不那么伤感的话题
On a less painful subject,
你穿多大号的T恤
what size T-shirt do you take?
拉杰  你是个体贴善良的好朋友
Raj, you were being a good friend,
生病不能作为我恶劣行为的借口
and my illness was no excuse for my behavior.
我希望你能接受我的道歉
I hope that you can accept my apology.
我当然接受
Of course I do.
还有  艾米丽  我很抱歉
And, Emily, I'm sorry for saying
说你们皮肤科医生不算真正的医生
dermatologists aren't real doctors.
我想这类言论你一定听腻了
And I'm sure you're tired of hearing that.
你真心觉得我常听到别人这么说吗
Do you honestly think I hear that a lot?
当你的工作尽是挤痘痘
Well, I would imagine when your job is popping zits
或者往老女人脸上注射肉毒杆菌时...
and squirting Botox into old lady faces...
打住
Okay!
够了  重点是
Okay, the point is
我们接受你的道歉
that we accept your apology.
也许你原谅了他
Uh, maybe you do.
但他刚才又侮辱了我一次
He just insulted me again.
但他不是故意的
Yeah, but he doesn't mean it.
你干嘛帮他说话
Why are you defending him?
这个问题我知道答案
I believe I can answer that.
和我一样
Uh, like me,
拉杰正在展示他的同理心
Raj is demonstrating empathy.
现在  你何不接受我的道歉
Now, why don't you accept my apology,
拿上你的免费T恤
receive your free T-shirt, uh--
特小号应该合适你吧
I hope extra small is okay.
不知道为啥沃罗维兹把中号拿走了
For some reason Wolowitz took a medium.
我不接受你的道歉
Well, I don't accept your apology.
你这是干什么呢
What are you doing?
这叫做为自己出头
It's called standing up for myself.
你偶尔也应该试试
You should try it some time.
好吧  那这样如何
Fine, how about this?
你拉长了这场无聊的争执
You're making me uncomfortable
让我很不舒服
by prolonging this ridiculous fight,
我希望你不要再闹了
and I wish you'd stop.
你希望我不要再闹了吗
Oh, you want me to stop?
没问题
No problem.
别这样  你别走啊
No, come on, please don't leave!
我想搞清楚  你还会去旅行吗
Point of clarification-- are you still going on the trip?
如果你不去的话...
Because if not...
别担心  你可以去
Don't worry, you're good.
是我引起了这场争吵  我觉得好内疚
I caused that fight, I feel terrible.
等等等等  我还可以演得更好...
Wait, I can do that better...
是我引起了这场争吵
I caused that fight.
人家觉得好内疚
I feel terrible.
我自己都分不清哪个演法更出色了
Yeah, wow, I don't know which one I like more.
他们吵得很糟糕吗
So, was the fight really bad?
不
No.
作为一场争吵  那真是恰到好处
As a fight, it was excellent.
她言辞激烈  摔门而去
She used harsh language and slammed the door.
虽然我也同时反应过来
Although as I say this,
你问的估计不是这个意思
that might not have been what you were asking.
他们还会去旅行吗
You think they'll still go on the trip?
我只知道我为了平息这场争吵去了艾米丽家...
All I know is after the fight I went to Emily's to smooth...
-他们不会去了吧  -是的
- They're not going on the trip. - No.
你这人到底什么毛病
What is wrong with you?
看看他  如此关心我有什么毛病
Look at him, caring about what's wrong with me.
这真是一等一的同理心啊
That is some top-shelf empathy.
我们应该组成一个俱乐部
Hey, well, we should start a club.
你去艾米丽家道歉
You went to Emily's to apologize.
等你走了以后  她就哭了
And when you left, she was crying.
这是真的
That is true.
我想我应该再道歉一次了
Well, I suppose I should apologize again.
她没事吧
Is she okay?
没事  我安抚了她
Yeah, I calmed her down.
但如果谢尔顿去赌城  她就不去了
But she's not going to Vegas if he's going.
等等  还有这个选项吗
Wait, that's an option?
我都不知道还有这个选项
I didn't know that was an option.
没关系  因为我决定
Well, that is fine, because I've decided
我不和你们去旅行了
that I won't be joining you.
因为我意识到最能表达
I've realized that the most genuine way
我的歉意的方式
to demonstrate the remorse I feel is
就是让你们自己好好享受这个周末
to let you have this weekend to yourselves.
你真成熟大度
That's very mature of you.
我自己最近也正在进行一段旅行
Well, I've been on a little trip myself recently.
不是去罪恶之都  而是去最善之城
Not to Sin City but to Sincere City.
去那里不会让你生殖器长性病
Where instead of genital warts, the only growth
而是心灵得到成长
you'll come back with is personal growth.
你下一件T恤的标语有了
And there's your next T-shirt.
看看这些脱衣舞舞杆
Ooh, check out the stripper pole.
你知道这是什么意思吧
You know what that means.
在上高速之前  拉杰就会吊在上面不下来
That Raj'll be on it before we make it to the freeway?
你猜对了
You know it!
这一切真是太酷了
This is so cool.
大家喝点香槟吧
Let's have champagne!
我先来一段祝酒词
Well, I would like to propose a toast
这个美好周末是大家应得的
to a well-deserved weekend of...
你在这里干什么
What are you doing?!
我原本计划在州边境跳出来的
My plan was to jump out at the state line,
但我的一个鼻塞掉进马桶里了
but one of my nose plugs fell into the toilet.
你就不能放过我们一个周末吗
You couldn't give us just one weekend?
我都说了这是个坏主意
I told him this was a bad idea.
我们该怎么办  把他们踢下车去吗
What do we do-- kick them off?
如果我们把他们丢在消防站
If we drop them off at a fire station,
消防员必须无条件收下他们[美国弃婴法]
they have to take them; no questions asked.
在你这么做之前  请再给我一次机会
Before you do, please give me one more chance
向艾米丽道歉
to apologize to Emily.
我的神啊
Oh, God.
艾米丽  我想你一定知道
Emily, as I'm sure you know,
我算是公认的怪人
I'm considered an odd fellow.
但你不知道的是
But what you don't know is that,
虽然我经常说错话
while I often say the wrong thing,
但我的本意并非想伤人
in my heart I mean well.
我觉得你是一个
I think that you are
聪明又美好的女人
a smart and wonderful woman, you know?
我们都觉得你配他
And we all think that you
是鲜花插在了牛粪上
can do better than Koothrappali.
我说谢尔顿...
You know, Sheldon...
嘘  让他说完
Shh, let him finish.
所以  为了之前我对你的多次冒犯
So, for all the times I've offended you
和未来我对你的多次冒犯
and all the times that I'll offend you in the future,
我向你道歉
I'm sorry.
谢谢你
Thank you.
很好
Good.
那我就准备下车了
Then I'll be leaving now.
没关系  谢尔顿
Oh, it's okay, Sheldon.
和我们一起去吧
Come with us.
你真是太好了
Oh, that's very kind of you.
但我相信没有我在  你们一定玩得更开心
But I'm sure you'll all have a better time without me.
我们走吧  斯图尔特
Let's go, Stuart.
可人家想留下一起玩
But I want to stay.
斯图尔特  赶紧的
Stuart, now!
虽然我知道他是个讨厌鬼
You know, I know he's a jerk,
但我还是觉得他很可怜
but I actually feel bad for him.
你现在知道问题所在了吧
And now you see the problem.
上来吧  你这个让人蛋疼的家伙
Come on, you pain in the ass!
他们指的是我
That's me!
回见了  斯图尔特
Bye, Stuart.
等等
Wait!
我也很让人蛋疼啊
I'm a pain in the ass, too!
你和拉杰能重修旧好
Are you relieved that you and Raj
你心里是不是也松一口气
were able to patch things up?
就现在来说吗
At the moment?
我不这么觉得
No, not really.
摇起来啊  宝贝
Shake it, baby!
电动小马达抖起来
Work that thing!